<post>
	<title>Test POST</title>
	<postdate>2016-12-31</postdate>
	<author>tibone</author>
	<text>
		Spicy jalapeno bacon ipsum dolor amet fatback tongue turducken turkey leberkas boudin andouille. Ground round pastrami strip steak buffalo, shankle prosciutto tenderloin filet mignon. Buffalo pancetta beef ribs picanha. Burgdoggen buffalo leberkas, short loin spare ribs doner bresaola fatback. Drumstick brisket doner, jowl ham boudin pig pork bacon short ribs rump pork loin meatloaf shankle spare ribs. Shank sirloin corned beef turducken kielbasa pig. Bresaola meatball pancetta, fatback t-bone shank turkey biltong pork chop.
		
		Spare ribs flank corned beef tri-tip. Sausage prosciutto pancetta jerky pastrami boudin tongue. Shoulder pork buffalo, andouille pancetta spare ribs porchetta sausage short loin shankle ground round sirloin pork loin. Tri-tip prosciutto ground round pig kielbasa, ham kevin frankfurter swine cupim buffalo capicola shoulder. T-bone spare ribs short ribs prosciutto beef ribs shank buffalo, tenderloin landjaeger alcatra frankfurter. Beef beef ribs chicken tongue.
		
		Tri-tip t-bone chuck filet mignon tenderloin, fatback bacon boudin. Beef ribs biltong ground round chicken capicola burgdoggen, pork loin flank tail t-bone spare ribs tenderloin swine pork chop. Meatball beef ribs bacon, picanha pork pork belly shank. Cupim short ribs pig ham hock meatloaf shoulder ribeye rump boudin pork capicola porchetta biltong picanha frankfurter. Leberkas t-bone venison sirloin pork loin biltong tenderloin prosciutto bresaola tongue shank. Tenderloin capicola andouille sausage beef ribs pork loin jowl short ribs pancetta meatloaf cupim. Tenderloin corned beef tail, porchetta burgdoggen kielbasa pork chop meatball sirloin pig pork landjaeger ribeye andouille.
		
		Drumstick prosciutto hamburger, cupim brisket shoulder rump frankfurter pastrami doner. Tail sirloin burgdoggen picanha salami beef rump kielbasa jowl. Flank pork belly sausage, ground round pork loin pig biltong meatloaf. Sirloin ball tip chicken venison doner. Chicken filet mignon burgdoggen tri-tip salami cow leberkas kielbasa capicola doner cupim andouille.
	</text>
</post>

